

# Ali Navidi **♀** Sari, Iran → +989339668289 2 years of experience

ali\_navidi24@yahoo.com Portfolio: alinavidi.dev/

Blog: dev.to/westernal

westernal 🕠 ali-navidi-850a80209 in westernal

ali-navidi 🖹

Junior Front-End Developer

A 22 years-old frontend developer and a recently computer (software) engineering graduate, coding since 2018 and over 2 years of experience in developing websites, trying my best to write clean code, higher up the performance and improve the user experience, always seeking to improve my abilities and learn new things.

Skills: Node.js MongoDB Tailwind Next.js HTML ) CSS Cypress Express.js SEO Git Bootstrap Svelte React.js JavaScript **TypeScript** Remix

## Experience

**Restarone Solutions Inc.** restarone.com

Sep 2022 to Dec 2022

Frontend Engineer Toronto, Canada

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Following SEO best practices.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.
- Fixing bugs and testing for usability.
- Creating tools that improve site interaction regardless of the browser.

Oben Origin co. Jan 2020 to Nov 2021

Frontend developer Tehran, Iran

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Following SEO best practices.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.
- Fixing bugs and testing for usability.
- Creating tools that improve site interaction regardless of the browser.

# Projects

### Westernal - FrontEnd

Westernal is a social media based on songs, you can share posts that includes part of a song, the whole song or music videos with your followers and let the music talk for you!

CSS, JavaScript, Next.js, Cypress

### Westernal - BackEnd

www.westernal.net/ github.com/westernal/social-media-backend

Westernal is a social media based on songs, you can share posts that includes part of a song, the whole song or music videos with your followers and let the music talk for you!

JavaScript, Express.js, MongoDB, Node.js

#### Cinema

github.com/westernal/Cinema

Watching and downloading movies website and progressive web app (PWA) with Next.JS and TypeScript

CSS, TypeScript, JavaScript, Next.js

#### sari-sartel

sari-sartel.com/ github.com/westernal/sari-sartel

Sari-sartel: a mobile and accessories shop.

CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

### **Dashboard**

Admin dashboard using Next JS

CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

## Education

Noshiravni University of Technology nit.ac.ir

Bachelor's of Science, Computer Engineering

Oct 2018 to Feb 2023

**Publications** 

**DEV Community** 

 $\label{eq:condition} \mbox{\it \ \ } \mbox{\it dev.to/westernal/introducing-westernal-a-social-media-based-on-songs-1pa9}$ 

## How do you write your CSS?

**DEV Community** 

Languages

Farsi Native

English Advanced